hey guys uh i know you guys are looking
at me like this dude's not gonna be
funny
looks like he's gonna give a lecture
about considering a career in law
enforcement
yeah if people don't think i'm going to
be funny you know they asked me for
directions a lot that happens a lot
it happened just outside the hotel you
know i don't know where anything and
this lady comes up
where's the post office where's the post
office you want to tell them something
so i was like
go straight make a right then another
right then another right when you get
back here
ask somebody who knows
good to be here in indiana jones's
living room
i'm a comedian my wife is a psychologist
so she uh
fixes people's problems all day i make
fun of them all night that's kind of how
that works
we live in brooklyn new york brooklyn
new york it's uh
it's kind of fancy now it's like dogs
with uggs and stuff
you but know did hear this argument out
of the window the other day one guy
shouts at another guy you know what the
real n word is
[Music]
[Laughter]
knowledge
you see stuff in brooklyn you don't see
anywhere else i was walking through the
park the other day i see this old man
doing tai chi i'm like oh that's cool
then i look closer it's not an old man
doing tai chi it's one of those heroin
guys it never falls over
[Laughter]
i think that's who designed this set i
think that's redesigned
i didn't grow up in brooklyn i grew up
in washington dc
i went to uh yeah i went to dc public
schools the only school system with
white history month
uh
i was the only white kid on my class for
the school play i was the snow storm i
just ran across stage naked
then i moved to new york i moved to
brooklyn and uh
my neighborhood was hostile when i moved
there like the first is 30 years ago the
first day i'm there getting a
confrontation
you know with this guy you know i ought
to i had to bust your face
i don't bust your face you stand on my
block you don't show no respect you look
in my
eye i had to bust your face i was like
look officer
i'm just trying to
[Music]
trying to acclimate myself so i'm a
jewish comedian married to a black woman
with a phd who looks like an indian we
live in an italian name in brooklyn
everybody thinks i'm puerto rican
you know so puerto ricans think i'm a
cop
uh
[Laughter]
i play a lot of cops and in shows and
stuff like that but
most of the time i play bad guys like uh
a while ago i had an audition
for a show called swift justice which
you can tell by the name
it's gonna be a really bad show you know
and i always play like flocco to drug
dealer and i have one line and the line
is i'm gonna cut you good
you know so practicing in the apartment
i'm doing to the cat you know i'm gonna
cut you good
you know do it to my wife i'm gonna cut
you good she's like take out the trash
i'm like
you know i memorized life so
i go to the audition the next day
there's 30 guys look just like me
sitting there we're gonna cut you good
you know i'm nervous
cass director comes out he messes up my
name dc benny's like
jc penny yeah come on
i walk in i'm so nervous i forget the
line so i improvise something i'm like
i'll kill all you fools and i just leave
right
and i get the part i get the parts right
it's like if i'm very excited you know
practicing we the day we shoot it we
shoot it everything's great and then uh
the night it comes on i tell everybody
my whole family was sitting there
watching the part comes
i'm nowhere to be found i'm like what
happened my wife said you got you good
hey did you know that dry bar comedy has
their own app download it right now to
watch and save and share clips
and you can watch my whole special